[
  {
      "title": "Funny"
  },
  {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Feck, drink, arse, women’s knickers",
      "answer": "Fr. Ted"
  },
  {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Monkey Tennis",
      "answer": "I’m Alan Partridge"
  },
  {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "One more facelift on this one, and she’ll have a beard",
      "answer": "Absolutely Fabulous"
  },
  {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "I suppose I’ve created an atmosphere where I’m a friend first, a boss second. Probably an entertainer third",
      "answer": "The Office"
  },
  {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "I’ve got a plan and it’s as hot as my pants",
      "answer": "Blackadder"
  },
  {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Instead you got a babe with a bob cut and a magnificent bosom",
      "answer": "The Vicar of Dibley"
  },
  {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Oh my god they killed Kenny",
      "answer": "South Park"
  },
  {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Sydney Opera House perhaps? The Hanging Gardens of Babylon? Herds of wildebeest sweeping majestically………….",
      "answer": "Fawlty Towers"
  },
  {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "If anyone is feeling anxious, worried or maybe just want a chat, please, please do not come crying to me",
      "answer": "Derry Girls"
  },
  {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Ah, stop it you’re a married man. Although if you are interested in that sort of thing you know I’m very open minded and discreet. Okay?",
      "answer": "Gavin and Stacey"
  }
]
